

DIAN **ANANDA**Web developer

O Jatisari, Bekasi - Indonesia

☑ dionananda77@gmail.com

% +62896-2777-3145

SOCIAL

in @dian-ananda

f @dion.ananda

@ @dionannd_

PROFILE

I am a front-end developer who mastered ReactJS, NextJS and JavaScript as a back-end and am learning to be a fullstack developer, experienced in using Laravel and Codelgniter frameworks, and currently learning Typescript, Flutter and Golang.

SKILLS

- HTML
- React
- CSS
- Express
- JavaScript
- Next
- TypeScript

LANGUAGES

Indonesia

English

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Freelance From 2021 to now | Towedd.com become an front-end developer landing page and app web.

OPERATOR MELTING

From 2019 to 2020 | Yamaha Motor Parts Mfg Indonesia become an operator of aluminum smelting, motorcycle wheel printing.

OPERATOR WRAPPING

From 2018 to 2019 | Suryaraya Rubberindo Industries become an inner and outer tire packaging operator.

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

From 2017 to 2018 | Wiennexindo Solution

become a junior programmer and start learning several programming languages.

EDUCATION

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

SMKN 4 Kota Bekasi

2015 - 2017

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL

SMPN 24 Kota Bekasi

2012 - 2014

PRIMARY SCHOOL

MI Attaqwa 28 Kota Bekasi

2005 - 2011

INTERESTS

Music Play Game Badminton Watch Movies